[ waves lapping ]
[ ♪ ♪ ♪ ]
[ grunts quietly ]
[ surfer shouting on video ]
[ speaking Spanish ]
[ speaks Spanish ]
[ surfer whooping ]
Oh-oh !
[ speaks Spanish ]
[ muffled screaming ]
[ screaming continues ]
[ boy panting ]
[ ♪ ♪ ♪ ]
Is that you on the beach ?
- Oh , no , no , that 's my , that 's my mom . - Oh .
Yeah . She came to this beach when she found out she was pregnant with me .
I 've never been , but , uh , it 's kind of our beach .
[ quiet laugh ]
That 's my little sister .
[ man ] Ah .
[ laughs ]
[ man speaking Spanish ]
Um , you want to see more photos ?
- I can ... - Um ...
[ speaking Spanish ]
It 's only for your eyes .
Real . Authentic .
You 're right .
Thank you .
Sorry . I 'm American .
[ chuckles ]
Not too many gringos here .
- Yeah , bummer . - Gracias a Dios .
[ woman laughs ]
♪ ♪ [ " Walk on the Wild Side " in Spanish , plays on radio ]
[ phone chimes ]
She 's not coming ?
- [ speaks Spanish ] - Uh , my-my friend .
You know , uh , mi amiga .
You know , the girl we left back at the hotel ?
You know , she smelled like Don Julio ...
and bad choices ?
She always does this to me , too .
She-she just , she just disappears .
She 's like the-the-the fantasmo , no ?
You know , you know fantasmo ?
- Fantasma , con " A. " - Sí , con " A. "
The whole reason I planned to come on this trip ,
con " A , " was-was-was to find the secret beach .
And now she 's just stuck back at Las Rocas
with the Irish flu .
[ sighs ]
[ speaking Spanish ] Nursing a hangover .
Sí . Major hangover . [ continues in Spanish ]
You-you don 't like it when someone
change your plans , do you ?
No , I don 't .
No , I don 't , it 's just , you know .
It 's not fair .
Ooh , you know why , though ?
It 's because I 'm reliable .
- You know " reliable " ? - Uh ...
" Reliable . " [ speaking Spanish ] Bossy .
Um , I am re-li-able .
[ electronic voice speaks Spanish ]
[ speaking Spanish ] Yes , bossy .
[ repeats in Spanish ]
That 's me . [ speaks Spanish ] Very bossy .
Hey , um ...
what is this beach called ?
You 're not gonna tell me .
Cool .
Cool . Frio .
[ speaks Spanish ]
Not possible .
It 's too hot here .
No , no , you 're cool . You 're being cool .
- Oh , never mind , that 's good . - [ laughs ]
All right , I got it .
♪ ♪ [ bright , jazzy music plays over radio ]
Is this the one ?
Sí .
[ ♪ ♪ ♪ ]
[ gull screeching ]
This is paradise .
Yeah . It 's perfect .
Uh ...
[ speaking Spanish ] This is the island
of the pregnant woman . No ?
La isla ?
No .
[ speaking Spanish ] Yes .
The nose ... the breasts ... and her stomach .
[ chuckling ] No .
[ woman chuckles ]
[ speaking Spanish ] Yes , it is for me .
Gracias .
Gracias , señor , um ...
- No , no , no . Por favor . - No , please .
Please . Please , I insist .
No , no , we were going the same way .
I live close by , so ... don 't worry .
Oh , are you sure ?
- Yes . - Okay . Well , thank you .
You 're welcome .
I 'm Nancy .
- Carlos . Charlie . - Nice to meet you , Charlie .
Nice to meet you .
[ speaking Spanish ]
Um , you know , have , high school .
You 're in school ?
No .
I mean , I was in medical school ,
but we didn 't have Spanish there , just cadavers .
I 'll shut up now . [ laughs quietly ]
Okay , uh , dark in a few hours , so ...
Oh , I never surf at night .
And , uh , how you
getting out from here ?
Uber .
Who is Uber ?
Never mind . Thank you , Carlos .
Thank you again for taking me here .
It means a lot to me .
- Okay . - Uh , what did you say
the name of it was again , though ?
I just forgot , for some reason .
[ speaking Spanish ] Careful .
[ speaks Spanish ] Always .
[ engine starts ]
[ ♪ ♪ ♪ ]
[ panting ]
Hey !
You speaking Spanish , guera ?
[ speaking Spanish ]
[ man speaking Spanish ]
I-I don 't understand . I 'm sorry .
He say that it is hard to paddle against the current .
Yeah , I wasn 't expecting that .
I almost got caught on the inside coming out .
[ speaking Spanish ]
- You American ? - Okay .
Sí . Sí , American .
Yeah !
California ?
Uh , close .
Texas .
There 's surf in Texas ?
Yes , we have surf in Texas .
It 's just not like this , though .
[ speaks Spanish ]
[ speaking Spanish ]
[ laughter ]
[ chuckles ]
Hey , this is a secret break .
How you find it ?
Someone told me about it a while ago .
What 's it called ?
If I tell you ,
I would have to kill you !
Well , that would ruin my day .
Anything gnarly out here , I should know about ?
There 's some rocks over there !
There 's only one tide a day ,
and when the tide gets low , it becomes an island .
There 's some nasty fire coral .
It stings like a jellyfish .
Okay ! Gracias .
Sí ... [ speaking Spanish ]
Hey , guera ...
[ speaking Spanish ]
Still have no idea what you 're saying .
He 's saying that you should come over here .
The wave breaks better .
Oh , I 'm okay , I 'm okay .
I 'm cool here , thank you .
Careful , gringa .
It 's rough out here for a little girl from Texas .
I think I 'll be all right .
iVámonos ! iVámonos !
[ speaking Spanish ]
[ ♪ ♪ ♪ ]
♪ I don 't look for trouble , but trouble looks for me ♪
♪ And it 's been waiting around corners since I was 17 ♪
♪ They say here comes a hurricane ♪
♪ Trouble is her middle name ♪
♪ But I don 't look for trouble ♪
♪ Yeah , trouble looks for me ♪
♪ Hey , hey ! ♪
♪ Hey ! ♪
[ whoops ]
[ laughter ]
[ shouting in Spanish ]
Oh !
[ laughs ]
[ whoops ]
[ ♪ ♪ ♪ ]
[ Nancy ] Yeah !
♪ Hey ! ♪
♪ Hey , hey ! ♪
♪ I don 't look for trouble ♪
♪ But trouble looks for me ♪
♪ Hey , hey ! ♪
♪ Hey ! ♪
♪ I don 't look for trouble ♪
♪ But trouble looks for me ♪
♪ Hey , hey ! ♪
♪ Trouble ! ♪
- ♪ Comes a hurricane ♪ - ♪ Trouble ♪
♪ Is my ... ♪
[ ♪ ♪ ♪ ]
[ surfers shouting in Spanish ]
[ phone chimes ]
- Short crop ? - Hey !
- Guess where I am ? - Tijuana .
[ laughs ]
Oh , my God . No way .
- Mom 's beach , right ? - It 's just as beautiful
as she said it was .
I wish you were here .
I wish she was here .
Does that mean you 're alone ?
Well , I wasn 't gonna come all this way just to wuss out
because I lost my plus one .
That 's how you wind up on Nancy Grace , okay ?
Excuse me .
I am supposed to be the boring , overprotective sister .
You are supposed to be the fun one .
Sis , the surf here , it 's insane .
You would not believe the perfect tube I just caught .
I could shoot tubes just as good as you ,
if you would just take me out !
I 'll take you . I 'll take you out as soon as I get back .
I love you , sister-mama .
- I love you , too , short crop . - [ man ] Is that Nancy ?
- It 's Dad . - Just tell him it 's all fine , okay ?
- Love you . Bye . - Uh , no , it 's , it 's a friend .
[ Dad ] Hey , Nance , don 't hang up .
Give me the phone . Chloe .
Hey !
Hey , Papa .
Hey , sweet pea .
Where now ?
Mexico .
I don 't know what to say , Nance .
I 'm at a loss . [ laughs ]
I don 't , I don 't , I can 't understand .
- I don 't expect you to . - Well , help me out , then .
I don 't know . What do you , uh , what do you want me to say ?
Oh , say you 're coming back .
Say you 're not dropping out of med school
after all this time , after all this work .
- You know , just don 't quit . - Okay . Okay , Dad .
That 's enough . Can we just
not do this right now , please ?
It 's what you love . You help people .
Well , not everyone can be helped , Dad .
You-you know that .
Don 't do that .
Don 't make this about her .
What else would it be about ?
If you want to make this about her , then you stay in it .
She was a fighter .
It 's just she fought too hard , Dad .
You know ? And for what ?
It all ended the same .
Just come back , Nancy .
Please .
I gotta go , okay ?
- I 'll see you soon . - When ?
- When ? - I don 't know .
Nance .
I love you . Bye .
[ ♪ ♪ ♪ ]
[ phone chimes ]
[ seabirds calling ]
[ slow , deep breathing ]
Yeah , girl , it 's getting late .
Let 's go in .
I 'm gonna catch one last one . Thanks .
Okay .
- Nice meeting you guys . - See you later , guera !
Buenas noches .
[ indistinct conversation ]
[ gasps ]
[ indistinct conversation in Spanish ]
[ indistinct conversation ]
[ screeching ]
[ water burbles ]
[ indistinct conversation ]
[ gasping ]
[ squeaking ]
[ squeaking , clicking ]
[ laughs ]
[ ♪ ♪ ♪ ]
[ birds screeching wildly ]
[ groans ]
[ exhales ]
[ grunts ]
[ ♪ ♪ ♪ ]
Oh !
[ muffled grunt ]
[ grunts ]
[ grunting ]
[ gasping ]
[ panting ]
[ gasps ]
[ muffled screaming ]
[ muffled scream ]
[ ♪ ♪ ♪ ]
[ yells , gasps ]
[ whimpering ]
[ panting ]
[ groans ]
[ gasping ]
[ screams ]
[ muttering ]
No !
[ groans ]
[ groans , sobs ]
Oh ...
[ panting ]
[ indistinct conversation ]
Help !
Hey !
Help me !
Help ... me !
I 'm here !
Help !
Yes . Yeah .
Here !
Here ! Here !
[ speaking Spanish ]
No !
Help !
[ sobbing ] Please , help me !
[ groans ]
[ panting ]
Come back !
[ ♪ ♪ ♪ ]
- [ rumbling ] - Oh , God ...
Oh , no , no , no .
Where are you taking me ?
[ panting ]
[ birds screeching ]
[ gasps ]
Too far .
[ whimpers ]
[ screeching ]
[ screams , grunts ]
[ groans , gasps ]
[ panting ]
[ groans echoing ]
[ ♪ ♪ ♪ ]
[ groan echoes ]
[ echoing gasps ]
[ screeches ]
[ gasps ]
[ chirps ]
Okay ...
Okay .
[ sighs deeply ]
[ groans ]
[ panting ]
You 're not gonna feel a thing , ma 'am .
I just put some Novocain injections to , uh ,
numb the area , so ...
you 're just gonna feel a little pressure , but ...
you 're not gonna feel the stitches , okay ?
Okay ?
[ screaming ]
[ groaning ]
Tie off the suture . Oh , yeah .
That 's a nice ... that 's a nice union .
[ groaning ]
One more , and then we 'll send you on your way .
[ sighing ] Okay . Here we go .
[ muffled scream ]
[ gasps , whimpers ]
Oh !
[ gasps , grunts ]
[ panting ] Okay .
Okay , ma 'am , nice clean wrap .
[ grunts ]
[ gasping ]
[ chirping ]
Get in line , buddy .
[ sighs ]
Just keep it elevated , ma 'am .
Someone 's coming .
Okay , okay ... you 're gonna be fine .
[ ♪ ♪ ♪ ]
[ metallic creaking ]
[ chitters ]
[ shuddering ]
- [ seagull squeals ] - [ Nancy groans ]
[ chittering ]
[ Nancy gasps , shudders ]
[ waves crashing in distance ]
[ whimpering ]
[ groans ]
[ panting ]
[ whimpering ]
[ groans ]
[ panting ]
There we go .
[ groaning ]
[ whimpering ]
[ blowing ]
[ sighs ] Gotta get some blood flowing .
Not enough flows in this tourniquet for you .
[ gasping ]
[ whimpering ]
Come on . Come on .
[ groaning ]
There we go .
[ groaning ] There we go .
[ grunts , then sighs ] Okay .
Okay .
[ groaning ]
[ sighing ] Okay , you get two minutes of blood flow .
Okay ... okay ...
[ groans loudly ]
Compression bandage .
- [ seagull screeches ] - Oh ! [ grunts ]
[ groans ]
[ groaning pain ]
[ screams ]
[ groans ]
[ screaming ]
[ gasps ]
[ shouting ]
[ groans ]
[ seagull squawking ]
[ squeals ]
[ gagging ]
[ seagull chitters ]
[ chittering ]
Ew .
[ gull chatters , squawks ]
[ ♪ ♪ ♪ ]
Are you still out there ?
Stay !
Good bird .
[ groans ]
Oh ...
[ gasps ]
[ ♪ ♪ ♪ ]
[ shudders ]
[ screaming in pain ]
[ groans ]
[ whimpering ]
[ gasping , whimpering ]
[ ♪ ♪ ♪ ]
Hello !
Hey !
[ continues , distantly ]
[ panting ]
[ distant ] Hello !
[ man groans softly ]
Yeah . Yeah !
Help !
Turn around !
Come on !
NANCY [ distant ] Hello ! [ shrieks ]
Hey !
Help !
Help me !
Yeah ! Hey ! Hey !
Help !
Call for help !
Wait , wait , wait , wait . My backpack .
My backpack ! It 's over there !
Yes ! Yes !
Over there !
iTeléfono !
Please , go get it !
Yes ! Yes !
Yes !
[ wincing ]
[ distant ] Open ! Inside !
Inside , the teléfono !
Telephone , please , hurry !
Come on !
[ chuckles ]
Please . Please .
Hurry !
No .
No , no , no .
No !
No , come back !
Come back , you can have it !
You can have it !
[ sobbing ] Come back !
Come back ! Please !
Please , help me !
Please !
[ sobbing ]
No .
No , there 's a shark !
[ distant ] A shark !
Wait ! It 's okay !
Just don 't go !
No ! There 's a shark !
Stop !
No !
Shark !
[ gasping ]
[ sighs ]
[ whimpering ]
- [ sudden splash ] - [ gasps ]
[ sobbing ]
[ gasping ]
[ birds singing ]
[ chittering ]
[ screeching ]
Shut up .
[ screeching continues ]
Shut up !
[ indistinct conversation ]
[ sighs ]
[ ♪ ♪ ♪ ]
Stop !
Stop ! Get out of the water !
Get out of the water !
Get out !
Stop !
Go back !
Shark !
Don 't worry about it !
There 's no sharks here !
Stop ! Stop !
Get out of the water !
Get out !
Go back ! Get help !
[ sighs quietly ]
[ squawks ]
[ gasps ]
[ screaming ]
[ grunting ]
Come on .
Come on !
Come on , come on ! Swim !
Come on , come on , swim !
Come on !
Come on ! I got you !
I got you ! Come on ! Come on !
Come on !
[ grunting ]
[ gasping ]
[ panting ]
[ speaks Spanish ]
[ speaking Spanish ]
Come on !
- [ speaks Spanish ] - I got you !
[ yells in Spanish ]
- I got you ! Come on ! - [ yells in Spanish ]
[ gasping ]
[ panting slowly ]
[ ♪ ♪ ♪ ]
[ gulls squawking ]
[ gull squawks ]
[ shudders ]
[ chirps , chitters ]
[ squawks ]
Come on .
[ chirps ]
[ squawks ]
Come on .
[ squawking ]
You 're okay .
I 'm helping you , little buddy .
Let me see you .
I 'm not very good at ortho , but ...
it just looks like a dislocation .
Like a separated shoulder .
[ sighs ] I think it 's the same .
We 'll see , huh ?
I 'm just gonna do this quick , okay ?
It 's gonna hurt just for a second ,
and then you 're gonna be okay .
On three . Ready ?
One ...
two ...
- three . - [ crack ]
- [ squawking ] - I think we did it .
Ah ! Ah ! Hey , hey , hey !
That 's a terrible way to say thank you .
[ gull chirps ]
Now you 've got a chance , huh ?
[ sighs ] And here comes the tide .
Camera .
That 's the third time .
I got you .
32 seconds from the whale to the rock .
[ sighs ]
[ beeps ]
[ gasps ]
[ gasping ]
[ grunting ]
[ muffled groan ]
[ beeping ]
[ groans ]
[ groaning , panting ]
[ panting ]
[ ♪ ♪ ♪ ]
[ grunts ]
[ gasping ]
[ snarling ]
[ Nancy yells ]
[ muffled screaming ]
[ ♪ ♪ ♪ ]
[ gasps ]
[ laughs ]
[ whooping ]
SURFER [ on video ] Ah , ha , ha ! Fuck !
[ garbled audio as video fast-forwards ]
iAyuda ! iAyuda !
[ surfer yells ]
NANCY [ on video ] Come on , I got you !
- [ surfer yells ] - I got you !
I got you ! I got you !
- Come on ! - [ surfer yells ]
Hold on !
Oh .
Someone got you .
30 , 40 yards .
One-minute swim .
I can make that .
I need a head start .
[ ♪ ♪ ♪ ]
This is Nancy Adams .
It 's April 26 , 2016 .
Uh , if you find this , please send help right away .
I 've been attacked by a shark .
He 's killed three other people since I got here .
He 's still circling , so ...
Uh , he 's got this big old whale over here ,
but that-that 's the problem .
I swam right up onto his feeding ground .
I 've been bitten pretty deeply
into my-my gastroc and quad muscles .
I have a-a deep gash running vertically
down my medial thigh ,
and then it turns lateral , just above my knee .
And right here , there ' s one going
across my , my posterior calf .
I 'm losing a lot of blood .
Gangrene is setting in .
I feel like I 'm losing my strength .
I don 't think I have much time .
The-the island I 'm on
is-is gonna be taken by the tide in a few minutes .
I 'm about 200 yards off the shore .
On this beach .
I never found out what it was called .
So ...
Um ...
This is useless .
There ' s a buoy ...
which I 'm gonna try to swim to ...
about 30 or 40 yards away .
So , yeah .
That 's ...
that 's the plan .
Um ...
If you find this , can you just , um ...
can you just delete that first part ,
and , uh , and send it to , uh ,
10231 Oliver Crescent Drive ,
Galveston , Texas .
That 's my home .
That 's-That 's where my , uh ,
that 's where my dad and sister live .
Yeah .
Hey , Pop .
Hey , Chlo .
Um ...
I finally got that alone time .
Super overrated .
[ chuckles ]
Uh ...
I mean I 'm not , I 'm not totally alone .
I got this little dude .
Steven Seagull here , keeping me company .
Show ' em your wing .
I fixed him for you , Chlo .
[ Steven chirps ]
I just don 't want you guys to worry ,
and I don 't want you to feel , um ,
you know , bad or anything , ' cause ...
[ sniffs ] I love you so much ,
and I miss you more than I ever ...
I ever even realized I could .
Dad , I gotta get off this rock soon ,
um ...
but I want you to know I 'm gonna fight .
I am .
Just like she taught us .
You were right .
[ chuckles ]
[ crying ]
I love you .
I love you so much .
Time to go .
[ ♪ ♪ ♪ ]
- [ squawking ] - It 's okay . It 's okay .
You got it . Good job .
You 're gonna make it , buddy .
You 're okay .
[ sighing ] Okay .
Okay .
[ chirps ]
[ ♪ ♪ ♪ ]
Shit .
Oh , you 're kidding me .
[ gasps ]
You didn 't like that ,
'cause it stings like jellyfish .
This is my head start .
[ gasping ]
[ inhales ]
[ muffled screaming ]
[ bellowing ]
[ gasping ]
[ ♪ ♪ ♪ ]
[ gasps ]
[ metallic creaking ]
[ screams ]
[ gasping ]
[ sighing ]
[ metallic creaking ]
[ gulls screeching ]
[ grunts , gasps ]
[ ship 's horn blows ]
[ creaking ]
[ gasps ]
[ grunting ]
Come on ...
Come on !
[ groans ]
[ gasps ]
Okay ...
[ groaning ]
[ groaning , gasping ]
[ sighs ]
[ metallic creaking ]
No , no , no , come back .
Come back .
Oh ... come back .
[ gasps ]
Come on .
Come back .
[ ♪ ♪ ♪ ]
[ sighing ]
[ gulls screeching ]
[ metal creaking , groaning ]
This is Nancy Adams .
It 's April 26 , 2016 .
Uh , if you find this , please send help right away .
I 've been attacked by a shark .
He 's killed three other people since I got here .
I 'm losing a lot of blood .
I feel like I 'm losing my strength .
[ voice-over ] I love you more , short crop .
I 'll be home soon .
[ Carlos speaking Spanish ]
[ Chloe ] No way . Mom 's beach , right ?
NANCY [ voice-over ] Not everyone can be helped .
I don 't want you to feel , you know , bad or anything .
I gotta go , Dad . I 'll see you later .
[ Dad ] Hey , sweet pea . ... she was a fighter .
[ Chloe ] I could shoot tubes ...
[ Nancy ] I 'm gonna fight ,
just like she taught us .
[ grunts , gasps ]
Uh-uh .
[ ♪ ♪ ♪ ]
- [ Nancy grunts ] - [ thud ]
[ grunts ]
Where are you ?
Fuck you .
[ gasps ]
Oh , shit .
[ Nancy whimpers , shouts ]
No ... no !
No !
[ panting ]
[ gasping , shuddering ]
[ screaming ]
No !
[ gasping ]
[ grunts ]
[ thudding , clanking ]
[ ♪ ♪ ♪ ]
[ inhales deeply ]
[ jaws snap ]
[ muffled yell ]
[ growling ]
[ panting ]
CARLOS : iMiguel !
[ speaking Spanish ]
[ panting ]
iPapá ! iPapá !
[ speaking Spanish ]
[ Carlos grunting , panting ]
iÓrale !
[ speaking Spanish ]
iÁndale ! iÁndale !
[ gasping anxiously ]
[ coughing ]
Relax . Relax .
Breathe . Breathe !
[ chittering ]
[ squawking ]
[ gasping , shuddering ]
[ breathing weakly ]
[ sighs ]
[ ♪ ♪ ♪ ]
I 'm okay .
Ready to get wet , Dr. Adams ?
Well , we 'll see about that .
Nancy ...
Ma would be proud of you .
Both of you .
Thanks , Papa .
Time to go .
♪ But there 's a scream inside ... ♪
Do you think I 'll ever be as good as you ?
- No . - [ Chloe laughs ]
♪ I don 't wanna die , no , I don 't wanna die ♪
♪ I don 't wanna die ♪
♪ No ♪
♪ And I don 't care if I sing off-key ♪
♪ I find myself in my melodies ♪
♪ I sing for love ♪
♪ I sing for me ♪
♪ I shout it out like a bird set free ♪
♪ No , I don 't care if I sing off-key ♪
♪ I find myself ♪
♪ In my melodies ♪
♪ I sing for love , I sing for me ♪
♪ I 'll shout it out like a bird set free ♪
♪ Oh , oh , oh-oh-oh ... ♪
♪ Oh , oh , oh , oh-oh-oh ♪
♪ Oh , oh , oh-oh-oh ♪
♪ Oh , oh ... ♪
♪ I 'll shout it out ♪
♪ Like a bird set free ♪
♪ Oh , oh , oh-oh-oh ... oh , oh ♪
♪ Oh-oh-oh ♪
♪ Oh , oh , oh-oh-oh ... ♪
♪ Oh , oh ♪
♪ I 'll shout it out like a bird set free ♪
♪ Oh , oh , oh-oh-oh ... ♪
♪ Oh , oh , oh-oh-oh ♪
♪ Oh , oh ... ♪
♪ I 'll shout it out like a bird set free ♪
[ song ends ]
[ ♪ ♪ ♪ ]
[ music ends ]